Time to get the jab in a foreign
country. Didn't see this coming. So, I
found out last night I will have to get
a yellow fever vaccine in order to
re-enter Costa Rica from Colombia. I did
not know that, so let's go get
vaccinated in a foreign country with
absolutely no preparation. So, I have a
30-minute walk down the streets of Cali.
You're walking on this little 2-ft
platform next to eight lanes of traffic,
dog. Some people got it pretty rough.
Woah. Good god, that's a lot of pigeons.
I have never seen more pigeons in one
place in my life. Well, I made it.
So, they're really nice. They gave me
this little appointment card, and here
we go. There's only like two or three
people ahead of me. Hopefully, I can get
this done today. It cost 120 million
pesos for this.
Uh I have no idea how much that is. It
is roasting in here. Ooh, Colombia, they
have vaccinations against cancer. Wonder
why I've never seen that in the US.
I have officially been vaccinated in a
foreign country. I guess there's a first
time for everything. Just remember that
everything happens for a reason.
Sometimes, the reason is you're stupid
and make bad decisions without knowing
things.